hey what's up I want to show you how you
can use the new chat GPT 40 the update
to it to do all your graphics design
Graphics
designers they the traditional way of
doing it through whether it be canva or
photoshop if you're a traditional as
Graphics designer like canva is not
traditional it has become more
traditional now chat GPT has replaced a
lot of those tools in One update and
I'll tell you this this is a brand new
version uh it's only going to get better
we're using it right now to help develop
graphics for Branding for a health
company that we're actually developing
out right now with a client here's a
brand that we were literally able to
create using chat GPT and then we we
able to help create some products and
stuff like that for the brand right
there so what I want to do is I want to
show you how you can actually use this
now you need to have chat GPT plus to be
able to do this so it is the paid
version it's $20 a month but the way
that it works is with GPT 40 you can
basically tell it to create any kind of
graphic and so I'm going to show you the
way that I like to do this myself and
one of the best ways is sure you can go
in here and say uh make me a
graphic
of a brand for a puppy dog grooming
company
um and you could just tell it to do that
but here's what I would would rather do
I would rather you say act as an expert
graphic
designer and
brainstorm an idea for a brand
for a puppy dog grooming company okay so
instead of it making the graphic I'm
going to first have it brainstorm the
idea for the brand for us this allows
you to have a lot more control over it
so let's say that we're going to call it
fluff uh snout okay we're going to call
it snouting
about here's the color palette ideas
right there um let's call it snouting
about generate for me uh three brand
profile ideas I can choose from for this
branding
okay uh love snouting about let's see
the wholesome Boutique
Vibe and and this is really cool is like
with chat GPT you can have it you can
just talk to it treat it like like it's
a like it's a a contractor that maybe
you hired to work for you uh somebody
who is a graphic design expert that you
hired to come in to your business and to
be able to help you with this okay uh
modern minimal on the- go or fun
Whimsical Community Driven I like fun
Whimsical Community Driven so let's take
this right here and I'm going to say
okay generate me a brand for
this here's a full brand package for
this okay awesome this is great now what
we're going to do is we're going to say
now take all of these
details and turn them into a
brand sheet with a
logo brand guidelines that can be
used and this is where it gets really
fun
so it's turning this in brand overview
visual identity okay great so again it's
brainstorming this what I really need to
do and this is where the part you might
be like gosh why is chat GPT not doing
what I want well because it's in a modus
operandi of answering our questions so
what we have to do is and I like this
information that it's giving me right
here is I want it to generate
us a I um I want you to take the above
and generate me an image for the
brand that I can see
visually and now here's where it's it's
going to do is it's going to start
generating this for us and then we could
take one of these pieces out such as the
logo such as a brand element and use
that um to refine it further and so chat
GPT used to like di 3 it used to be able
to generate images and things like this
but they weren't that great now you can
literally use what it generates in your
Marketing in your business on your
flyers in your logos and all of that on
your website again we just we just
launched a webinar uh this past week
where we were able to come up with the
stock images for this I'm going to I'm
going to show you this webinar it's not
fully launched right now but I'm going
to show you like what we were able to
come up with uh for this this is a
webinar all about uh gp1s this is for a
client that we're working with to help
them with this so we literally have a a
brand logo with products right there we
have a logo for the company we have a
stock image right there we have a logo
for the class itself this was all
generated using chat GPT we didn't have
to go into canva or anything to be able
to be able to do those okay so now it is
generating us this brand identity Bas on
this look at that snouting about where
Tails wag and Bubbles pop that is
incredible like right away that is just
mind-blowingly incredible and if you
wanted to turn this into a uh like a
vector you could import this into
there's a tool uh I believe it's called
recreate doai let me see is that it no
re AI I convert image to
Vector AI there's an AI tool that does
this that you can use that's really
great at this um that I found recraft
that's what it is recraft doai so
recraft AI does a really great job it
could actually take this output from
chat GPT turn it into a vector and you
could literally blow that up to use in
your business which is amazing but you
could also just use this for a number of
other things just by kind of copying
this not you have your brand identity
your
logos your uh Graphics everything is all
laid out right here that you could use
for your business now let's
say that I wanted to whoopsy let's go
back to chat GPT
here chat GPT let's say that I wanted to
use
this to create some create some branded
stock images of a truck that does the
dog grooming that uses this logo and
colors and
shows someone using the
service okay I'm telling you this is
like this is this is like magic right
here I can and and I want to copy and
paste the image into this and again what
I might do is I could have it brain
brainstorm what the image would look
like what the photograph would look like
and that would help it come up with
something that's even more um well
thought out planned out but just telling
it what you wanted it to do as well as
another great way to kind of take the
idea take the concept and see what the
AI can come up with okay so this is
really cool because again Graphics
designers can use this I'm going to show
you some other ideas while it's loading
that that we did and what we came up
with and how we how we're using this in
our business
one thing that I just did recently was I
went through and I
created a let me see I took a photo of a
robot from Tesla and a photo of my
kitchen and I combined it and I told it
to literally put the Tesla robot in my
kitchen so it's a photograph of my
kitchen a photograph of the robot and it
was able to combine that into a photo of
my kitchen with the robot and I thought
that was really really cool that I was
able to do that just with one single
prompt I then was like okay have a
picture of me hugging the robot now the
face looks a little bit weird I'm trying
to figure out how to maybe swap the face
out make it look a little bit better but
yeah here's me right there and I told
her add me into a shot hugging the robot
in the same location in my kitchen and I
was like okay make it you know like my
face Stu like that but yeah I've been
playing around with that now another
thing that I was able to do is I was
able to make a series of
reals
about regulating your nervous system and
at first it started creating the reels
with this
character but then what I thought was as
it generated it I I decided to tell it
can you make the character look more
like me so I was able to create all of
these little Graphics that tell a story
it literally generated these based on
the text that it was given and the
concept and then what I did was I took a
photo took photos of me and I told it
make
me as the person in the
graphic and it literally was able to go
ahead and instead of this random guy
that it generated it took my face turned
me into a little
cartoon and put that in there and it
honestly like it looks awesome
so this is another just great use case
that you could do you create little mini
cartoons Instagram reels things like
that you could use for your business
okay let's go back and see the the oh
look at that there it is there's our
truck right
there okay watch this okay
brainstorm a high-end
branding photo to use that improves the
idea of
above give all details for the photo
shoot and this is something that I love
to do this is a prompt that I love to do
for images like this is it's now going
to take its Ai and brainstorm way to
highlight it as a premium brand and
things like that okay camera angles all
of that now what we're going to do is
this is how I like to do it I like to
copy the image paste it back into chat
GPT take The Branding sheet so that it
has the brand and then I'm going to take
it's
brainstormed high-end photo
shoot I'm going to paste that back down
there and I'm going to say generate this
image and so now what it does is it's
literally going to generate the high-end
image that it just brainstormed so the
AI isn't able to like kind of come up
with that image first the idea concept
and then do that but if we do like a
three-step process with this and you can
do this for like any kind of image that
you can up with where we okay we came up
with a brand
idea
we have the brand right here okay now we
have an image not the greatest image
looks looks kind of AI
generated but now we had the AI
brainstorm as a high-end branding photo
shoot brought all those pieces
together and now we can see what it
comes up with and I'm and I'm telling
you this is going to look awesome
you're going like it's going to it's
going to upscale and uplevel what the
image looks like because it takes into
mind all of the different features from
how we want the eyes of the human and
the dog the tagline ideas of the camera
how we want the camera even set up like
you know look at this you can literally
see already the
lighting of the truck the framing of the
shot this looks like a
high-end
company that you might
hire to be able to do something like
this and so you can
literally build a
business and have branding
photos that look incredible okay so the
brand does not match on her shirt that's
where what we might do is we might take
this the okay the the text doesn't match
right there so this is where some of the
little limitations that we run into with
this and this is where it's going to get
a little bit better you can highlight
this right here we can highlight that
and we can correct it we can tell it
okay I want the text to say Glam On The
Go and we need her shirt to say
snout and
about okay so it's able to kind of take
the selection it should be able to
correct those sections for us either way
again just the concept of being able to
do that being able to take these ideas
and come up with them and and create
something that you could use for your
marketing that quickly as photos and
logos and things like that is just
really absolutely incredible um again
okay let's take this concept and let's
say let's generate uh an
Instagram Carousel idea based on this
brainstorm a carousel idea based on this
brand and maybe we can open up a new
chat GPT window to do this that way it
can it can still come up with the the
logos and the images and all that and
then we're going to copy like our let's
see our our
brand
information info this is how I like
quickly can do this is open up a new
window okay I don't want it to actually
generate me the
image so that's the problem there is it
started generating me the
image I guess it says it generate I told
it to generate so we have to use the
word
brainstorm let's
brainstorm an
Instagram Carousel idea
and now it's going to actually it's
still generating the image it's probably
because we have so much information that
we pasted in about an image so let's
just go back
here and kind of see what it's
generating for this we go back to
that that's where again some of the
limitations of how this all works can be
a little tricky okay Great Glam On The
Go Stout and about probably crop it
right here do that okay great now
let's uh brainstorm together via text
and I might need to tell it that
brainstormed together via text in
Instagram Carousel idea uh Glam On The
Go slide one okay
great make this as a
cartoon that I could use
brainstorm five cartoon styles for the
uh carousel
turning into a cartoon style is genius
make the brand lovable soft pastel
storybook style okay that's maybe one
version that we might want to want to
play
with bold pop art actually yeah let's do
bold pop art
style comic strip okay let's do bold pop
art
style we're going to to pull up the
slides slide breakdown we're going to
take the branding
images we're going to take these
different images that had already
generated as
inspiration for the
style okay
and then we're going to tell it
to generate slide one
using the following parameters and
style okay so we pasted all that in
there it generated all those ideas and
now we're going to see what it can use
to generate a slide one and then you'll
probably have to kind of copy and paste
all this until it just generates slide
two slide three slide
four and you can refine them
later but again for your marketing for
ideas for your
marketing this is just
brilliant okay so one problem I'm seeing
already this is not a square so again
for an Instagram Carousel with it not
being a square we might need to tell it
to make it a square but let's just see
what idea it generates first for this
all right
can take a little while to to to kind of
render the idea
out because it kind of goes top to
bottom right
here but this is brilliant what it's
like inside the cute what's it like
inside the cutest dog spa on Wheels so
again this is all just literally AI
generated
idea that it's now taking and it's
translating it into a different art
style that you could use and there's so
many different ways that you could
literally use this it's almost making it
kind of like Scooby-Doo now but still
using our same brand because we gave it
that brand
idea come spend the day with
us this is so cool snout and about it's
got the logo it's consistent
we got the character right
here this is so cute and awesome wag
okay great awesome okay now let's say
we're going to generate slide
two based on those
parameters to generate slide two okay so
slide one happy puppy and Van what's it
like inside come spend the day with us
meet Coco introducing the friendly
client dog this is Coco she's about to
get snouted yes it's a thing
little idea Coco stepping out of the
ging table okay so it's generating us
again based on that idea something that
we we could use and I'm not going to go
through like the whole ideas but you
could see how in your business this can
come up with so many different ideas
that you could use just using chat GPT
to do this it's Limitless as far as how
you could do this you could create
physical products you could have a
person holding the physical product like
I did with the uh the robot image right
like we did with the GP 1's image type
of a thing so there's so many different
ways that you could combine whatever
your mind can imagine you could then
have the AI come up with ideas for how
to frame it and put it together and then
it can generate that visual for you with
extreme detail so it's
amazing it's incredible and I highly
recommend you use it listen if you are a
coach Mentor trainer and you want to
know how to get more clients in your
business go check the link below I help
coaches mentors and trainers use social
media online marketing artificial
intelligence to scale their businesses
and to get tens of thousands of clients
every single month to make hundreds of
thousands of dollars a year and even
millions of dollars a year in their
business I've been doing this for 22
years and I can help you as well to do
this this is just one of the ways that
we help people do that is showing them
how to do things like this Here's the
final graphic that it generated pretty
awesome just that one idea right right
there I'd love to help you take this
further to help you get more clients in
your business that's what I help people
do every single week inside of my
wealthy coach Academy so click the link
in the description and I'll see you over
there we'll talk soon